Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Film and Video by Sport, 1937-2006 (Boxes 101-154), 198865
  - Football 1937-1946, 200449; Formats:DVD, VHS (Box 106)
    - 1945 Rice 13 | TCU 14 TRT 29:35, 200457
    - 1945 Rice 14 | Baylor 17 (incomplete - missing first 10 minutes) TRT 33:54, 200456
    - 1945 Rice 6 | Texas A & M 0 TRT 35:21, 200455
    - 1945 Rice 26 | Arkansas 7 TRT 34:14, 200454
    - 1946 Rice 21 | SMU 7 TRT 30:04, 200453
    - 1946 Rice 25 | Tulane 6 TRT 37:36, 200452
    - 1946 Rice 38 | Baylor 6 TRT 37:42, 200451
    - 4 Football games filmed by C. Boyd Kilgore, 1939-1942; 200450
      Games
      Missing Title
      Rice v. Vanderbilt, 1939
      Rice v. Baylor, 1939
      Rice v. A&M, 1941
      Rice v. Texas, 1942
  - Football 1947-1952, 200423; Formats:DVD, VHS (Box 107)
    - 1947 Rice 26 | Arkansas 7 (incomplete - missing part of 1st quarter) TRT 32:20, 200448
    - 1947 Rice 40 | Texas Tech 7 TRT 34:47, 200447
    - 1947 Rice 7 | TCU 0 TRT 28:38, 200446
    - 1947 Rice 7 | USC 7 TRT 31:12, 200445
    - 1947 Rice 41 | Texas A & M 7 (incomplete - ends at end of 3rd quarter) TRT 32:02, 200444
    - 1947 Rice 14 | LSU 21 TRT 26:54, 200443
    - 1948 Rice 7 | Baylor 7 (incomplete - missing first 7 minutes) TRT 28:28, 200442
    - 1948 Rice 0 | USC 7 TRT 34:21, 200441
    - 1949 Rice 55 | New Mexico 0 (incomplete - starts end of 2nd quarter, stops near end, very dark) TRT 16:20, 200440
    - 1949 Rice 41 | SMU 27 TRT 42:38, 200439
    - 1949 Rice 14 | Arkansas 0 TRT 35:43, 200438
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color silent film footage by Bob Bailey Studio featuring 35 minutes, 38 seconds of the football game played between the William M. Rice Institute and the University of Arkansas on November 5, 1949. Views of the Rice campus and downtown Houston can be seen in the background. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1949 Rice 7 | LSU 14 (incomplete - missing first 5 minutes) TRT 23:26, 200437
    - 1949 Rice 13 | Texas A & M 0 (incomplete - missing part of 1st quarter) TRT 31:36, 200436
    - 1950 Rice 7 | Texas 35 TRT 31:42, 200435
    - 1950 Rice 7 | Texas 35 TRT 45:42, 200434
    - 1950 Rice 27 | N. Carolina 13; Cotton Bowl 1-1-50 TRT 40:05, 200433
    - 1950 Rice 35 | LSU 20 TRT 31:40, 200432
    - 1950 Rice 13 | Texas Tech 7 TRT 27:13, 200431
    - 1951 Rice 42 | Texas A & M 45 (incomplete) TRT 25:05, 200430
    - 1951 Rice 13 | Baylor 34 TRT 44:40, 200429
    - 1951 Rice 21 | Navy 14 TRT 37:06, 200428
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Black and white silent film footage presented by Humble Oil, featuring 37 minutes, 12 seconds of a football game played between The William M. Rice Institute and the United States Naval Academy on October 13, 1951. There are scenes from the bleachers and of the teams warming up on the field before the game starts. Two men are seen shaking hands and talking after the game is over. Original resource is a black and white video.
    - 1951 Rice 14 | Clemson 20 TRT 42:08, 200427
    - 1951 Rice 28 | Texas A & M 13 TRT 33:34, 200426
    - 1952 Rice 16 | Texas A & M 6 TRT 27:54, 200425
    - Orange Bowl Committee, Rice vs. Tennessee 1947-1997, 200424
  - Football 1952-1954, 200393; Formats:DVD, VHS (Box 108)
    - 1952 Rice 34 | Texas Tech 7 TRT 36:31, 200422
    - 1952 Rice 12 | TCU 6 TRT 33:45, 200421
    - 1952 Rice 7 | Texas 20 TRT 31:48, 200420
    - 1952 Rice 16 | Texas A & M 6 TRT 29:54, 200419
    - 1952 Rice 0 | UCLA 20 TRT 26:11, 200418
    - 1952 Rice 20 | Baylor 14 TRT 29:27, 200417
    - 1952 Rice 14 | SMU 21 TRT 32:20, 200416
    - 1952 Rice 7 | Wisconsin 21 TRT 37:06, 200415
    - 1952 Rice 20 | Baylor 14 TRT 30:26, 200414
    - 1953 Rice 7 | SMU 12 TRT 28:54, 200413
    - 1953 Rice 20 | Florida 16 TRT 38:35, 200412
    - 1953 Rice 47 | Arkansas 0 TRT 33:48, 200411
    - 1953 Rice 40 | Hardin-Simmons 0 TRT 33:46, 200410
    - 1953 Rice 18 | Texas 13 TRT 32:20, 200409
    - 1953 Rice 28 | Cornell 7 TRT 36:28, 200408
    - 1953 Rice 19 | TCU 6 TRT 33:13, 200407
    - 1953 Rice 34 | Texas A & M 7 TRT 42:47, 200406
    - 1953 Rice 41 | Baylor 19 TRT 42:38, 200405
    - 1953 SWC Highlights & 1954 Cotton Bowl Highlights, 200404
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage from Humble Oil and Refining Company, featuring 23 minutes of the 1953 Southwest Conference highlights of William M. Rice Institute, University of Texas, Baylor University, Southern Methodist University, University of Arkansas, Texas A and M University and Texas Christian University. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1954 Rice 20 | Baylor 14 TRT 30:31, 200403
    - 1954 Rice 13 | Texas 7 TRT 30:50, 200402
    - 1954 Rice 7 | Wisconsin 13 TRT 38:04, 200401
    - 1954 Rice 29 | Texas A & M 19 TRT 31:50`1, 200400
    - 1954 Rice 34 | Vanderbilt 14 TRT 38:23, 200399
    - 1954 Rice 20 | Baylor 14 (incomplete - missing first 10 minutes) TRT 30:47, 200398
    - 1954 Rice 6 | SMU 20 TRT 30:48, 200397
    - 1954 Rice 34 | Florida 14 TRT 35:14, 200396
    - 1954 Rice 6 | TCU 0, 200395
    - 1954 Rice 21 | Texas A & M 34 (Freshman Game), 200394
  - Football 1954-1957, 200364 (Box 109)
    Scope and Contents note
    Formats:DVD, VHS
    - 1954 Rice 6 | TCU 0 TRT 31:10, 200392
    - 1954 Rice 21 | Texas A & M 34 (Freshman Game) TRT 32:05, 200391
    - 1954 Cotton Bowl Highlights, 200390
    - 1955 Rice 20 | Alabama 0 TRT 26:47, 200389
    - 1955 Rice 21 | Clemson 7 TRT 24:49, 200388
    - 1955 Rice 21 | Clemson 7 (end zone) TRT 23:20, 200387
    - 1955 Rice 0 | SMU 20 TRT 26:15, 200386
    - 1955 Rice 0 | Arkansas 10 TRT 25:25, 200385
    - 1955 Rice 0 | Arkansas 10 (end zone) TRT 25:23, 200384
    - 1955 Rice 20 | LSU 20 TRT 34:24, 200383
    - 1955 Blue-Gray Game, 2/26/55 TRT 36:01, 200382
    - 1955 Rice 7 | Baylor 15 TRT 24:53, 200381
    - 1955 Rice 0 | TCU 35 TRT 24:34, 200380
    - 1955 Rice 14 | Texas 32 TRT 31:17, 200379
    - 1956 Rice 17 | TCU 20 TRT 30:56, 200378
    - 1956 Rice 0 | Florida 7 TRT 25:55, 200377
    - 1956 Rice 7 | Texas A & M 21 TRT 27:21, 200376
    - 1956 Rice 27 | Utah 0 TRT 28:27, 200375
    - 1956 Rice 12 | Arkansas 27 TRT 38:15, 200374
    - 1957 Rice 13 | Arkansas 7 TRT 31:14, 200373
    - 1957 Rice 27 | SMU 21 TRT 27:49, 200372
    - 1957 Rice 34 | Stanford 7 TRT 26:54, 200371
    - 1957 Rice 7 | Clemson 20 TRT 25:17, 200370
    - 1957 Rice 6 | Duke 7 TRT 28:49, 200369
    - 1957 Rice 20 | TCU 0 TRT 39:00, 200368
    - 1957 Highlights, 200367
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy mp4.
    - 1957 Rice University Highlights TRT 12:00, 200366
    - 1957 Rice vs. Texas A & M; 1958 Rice vs. Navy (Cotton Bowl), 200365
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Black and white silent film footage filmed by Walter Scott and produced by Bob Bailey Studio, Houston Texas featuring 48 minutes, 28 seconds of the annual Cotton Bowl Football Classic played between the William M. Rice Institute and the United States Naval Academy on January 1, 1958, in Dallas Texas. Original resource is a black and white video.
  - Football 1958-1961, 200336 (Box 110)
    - 1958 Rice 7 | Army 14, 200363
    - 1958 Rice 24 | Arkansas 0, 200362
    - 1958 Rice 6 | LSU 26, 200361
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color silent film footage featuring 31 minutes of the 1958 William M. Rice Institute vs Louisiana State University football game. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1958 Rice 22 | TCU 10, 200360
    - 1958 Rice 21 | Texas A & M 28, 200359
    - 1958 Rice 16 | SMU 8 Freshman Game, 200358
    - 1958 Rice 13 | SMU 7, 200357
    - 1958 Rice vs. Navy (Cotton Bowl); 1953 Highlight Film, 1958 Highlight Film, 200356
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. The first part of this video features black and white silent film footage by Bob Bailey Studio of the 1958 Cotton Bowl game played by the William M. .Rice Institute and the United States Naval Academy. The second part of the video which starts at the 00:43:45 time mark features highlights from the 1958 Southwest Conference football games in color and with sound. This portion of the tape is presented by Humble Oil and Refining Company and is narrated by sportscaster Kern Tips. Original resource is a partially black and white, partially color, video.
    - 1959 Rice 3 | LSU 26, 200355
    - 1959 Rice 21 | Baylor 23, 200354
    - 1959 Rice 6 | Texas 25, 200353
    - 1959 Rice 7 | Duke 24, 200352
    - 1959 Rice 7 | Texas A & M 2, 200351
    - 1959 Rice 13 | Florida 13, 200350
    - 1959 Rice 0 | Clemson 19, 200349
    - 1959 Rice 6 | TCU 35, 200348
    - 1960 Rice 30 | Texas Tech 6, 200347
    - 1960 Rice 21 | Texas A & M 14, 200346
    - 1960 Rice 10 | Florida 0, 200345
    - 1960 Rice 7 | Baylor 12, 200344
    - 1960 Rice 10 | Tulane 7, 200343
    - 1960 Rice 0 | Arkansas 3, 200342
    - 1960 Rice 13 | Georgia Tech 16, 200341
    - 1961 Rice 10 | SMU 0, 200340
    - 1961 Rice 0 | Georgia Tech 24, 200339
    - 1961 Rice 7 | Texas 34, 200338
    - 1961 Rice 42 | Texas Tech 7, 200337
  - Football 1961-1964, 200307 (Box 111)
    Separated Materials note
    - 1961 Rice 0 | Arkansas 10, 200335
    - 1961 Rice 16 | LSU 3, 200334
      Contents include: DVD vob master and mp4 of the Rice Owls football game against LSU.
    - 1961 Rice 19 | Florida 10, 200333
    - 1962 Rice 15 | Baylor 28, 200332
    - 1962 Rice 7 | SMU 15, 200331
    - 1962 Rice 14 | Texas Tech 0 Missing 1st quarter, 200330
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color silent film footage featuring 32 minutes of most of the 1962 Rice University vs Texas Tech University football game. Missing 1st quarter. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1962 Rice 14 | Texas 14, 200329
    - 1962 Rice 23 | Texas A & M 3, 200328
    - 1962 Rice 14 | Arkansas 28, 200327
    - 1962 Rice 7 | Penn St. 18, 200326
    - 1963 Rice 7 | Arkansas 0, 200325
    - 1963 Rice 7 | Penn State 28, 200324
    - 1963 Rice 17 | Texas Tech 3, 200323
    - 1963 Rice 33 | TCU 7, 200322
    - 1963 Rice 7 | Arkansas 0, 200321
    - 1963 Rice 21 | LSU 12, 200320
    - 1963 Rice 13 | SMU 7, 200319
    - 1963 Rice 6 | Texas 10, 200318
    - 1963 Rice 6 | Texas A & M 13 Missing last few plays, 200317
    - 1963 Rice 12 | Baylor 21, 200316
    - 1963 Rice 23 | Stanford 13, 200315
    - 1964 Rice 20 | Baylor 27, 200314
    - 1964 Rice 0 | LSU 3, 200313
    - 1964 Rice 3 | Texas 6, 200312
    - 1964 Rice 0 | LSU 3, 200311
    - 1964 Rice 3 | Texas 6, 200310
    - 1964 Rice 7 | Stanford 34, 200309
    - 1964 Rice 24 | West Virginia 0, 200308
  - Football 1964-1968, 200278 (Box 112)
    - 1964 Rice 7 | SMU 6, 200306
    - 1965 Rice 13 | Texas A & M 14, 200305
    - 1965 Rice 21 | Duke 41, 200304
    - 1965 Rice 0 | Arkansas 31, 200303
    - 1965 Rice 0 | Texas Tech 27, 200302
    - 1965 Rice 14 | LSU 42, 200301
    - 1965 Rice 14 | SMU 17, 200300
    - 1965 Rice 14 | La. Tech 0, 200299
    - 1965 Rice 14 | TCU 45, 200298
    - 1965 Rice 20 | Texas 17, 200297
    - 1965 Rice 14 | Baylor 17, 200296
    - 1966 Rice 24 | UCLA 27, 200295
    - 1967 Rice 6 | Texas 28, 200294
    - 1967 Rice 9 | Arkansas 23, 200293
    - 1967 Rice 21 | Navy 7, 200292
    - 1967 Rice 14 | SMU 10, 200291
    - 1967 Rice 3 | Texas A & M 18, 200290
    - 1967 Rice 10 | Texas Tech 24, 200289
    - 1967 Rice 27 | Baylor 25, 200288
    - 1967 Rice 10 | TCU 14, 200287
    - 1967 Rice 50 | Northwestern 6, 200286
    - 1968 Rice 0 | Tennessee 52, 200285
    - 1968 Rice 35 | Washington 35, 200284
    - 1968 Rice 21 | Arkansas 46, 200283
    - 1968 Rice 7 | LSU 21, 200282
    - 1968 Rice 14 | Texas A & M 24, 200281
    - 1968 Rice 15 | Texas Tech 38, 200280
    - 1968 Southwest Conference Highlights, 200279
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage of Humble Oil and Refining Company, featuring 30 minutes of 1968 Southwest Conference football game highlights of University of Arkansas, University of Texas, Southern Methodist University, Texas Tech University, Baylor University, Texas A and M University, Texas Christian University and Rice University. Original resource is a color video.
  - Football 1968-1994, 200248 (Box 113)
    Formats:Beta, DVD, VHS
    - 1968 Rice 14 | TCU 24, 200277
    - 1969 Southwest Conference Highlights, 200276
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage by Humble Oil and Refining Company, featuring 28 minutes of 1969 Southwest Conference Football highlights from games played by Rice University, Texas A and M University, Texas Christian University, Texas Tech University, University of Texas, Baylor University, Southern Methodist University and University of Arkansas. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1970 Cotton Bowl Game, 200275
    - 1972-75 Rice University Highlights, 200274
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage featuring 1 hour and 18 minutes of Rice University football highlights between 1972 thru 1975. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1978 Rice vs. Texas, Arkansas, Texas A & M, 200273
    - 1978 Rice 19 | Iowa St. 23 Missing last 1:00, 200272
    - 1979 Rice vs. Texas, TCU, 200271
    - 1979 Rice vs. Tulane, Lamar, Texas Tech, 200270
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color silent film footage featuring 2 hours and 5 minutes of the 1979 football games of Rice University vs Tulane University, Rice University vs Lamar University and Rice University vs Texas Tech University. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1979 Rice vs. Arkansas, LSU, Oklahoma, 200269
    - 1979 Rice vs. Texas Tech, Texas AM, 200268
    - 1985 Rice vs. Air Force, 200267
    - 1987 Shows #1 thru #4, 200266
    - 1987 Rice vs. Arkansas, Baylor, UH, 200265
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color silent film footage featuring 1 hour and 38 minutes showing portions of the 1987 football games of Rice University vs. Arkansas, Rive University vs. Baylor University and Rice University vs University of Houston. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1987 Rice vs. LSU, SWT, Texas, 200264
    - 1987 Footage Highlights, 200263
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage featuring 46 minutes of 1987 Rice University football game highlights. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1989 Wake Special Teams vs. Rice, 200262
    - 12.8.90 Rice vs. Georgetown, 200261
    - 1991 Trevor Cobb Highlights, 200260
    - 1991 Trevor Cobb Highlights, 200259
    - 1991 Trevor Cobb Highlights, 200258
    - 1991 Matt Sign Rice Univ. Highlights, 200257
    - 1992 Rice Football Southwest Conference Presentation, 200256
    - 1992 Winners, 200255
    - 1992 Southwest Conference Highlights, 200254
    - 2.18.92 Rice vs. Houston, 200253
    - 1993 College Football The Quest for #1, 200252
    - 11.26.93 Houston at Rice E Game, 200251
    - 1994 Rice vs. Texas Highlights ESPN, 200250
    - 1994 Rice Owls Football Preview Mixed audio Rice vs. Houston, 200249
  - Football 1994-1998, 200203 (Box 114)
    Formats:Beta, VHS
    - 1994 Rice 17 | SMU 10 2nd half, 200247
    - 10.16.94 ESPN Rice University vs. University of Texas, 200246
    - 1994 Poised for the future WAC, 200245
    - 10.8.94 Rice Beats Texas Tech 24-21 Highlights for QB Club, 200244
    - 1994 Rice Football Highlights, 200243
    - 1994 Univ of Houston, 200242
    - 1995 Rice University Football Season Highlights, 200241
    - 10.21.95 Iowa State vs. Colorado, 200240
    - 1995 Winslow Young Drills, 200239
    - 9.2.96 Yo-yo champ, 200238
    - 1996 Highlights, 200237
    - 9.14.96 QB Club Rice 21 | Tulane 14, 200236
    - 1996 QB Club Rice vs. SMU/UTEP Fri night Tape, 200235
    - 1996 New Owl logo Football shots, 200234
    - 1996 Rice Football highs, 200233
    - 1996 Rice Owl Football highs, 200232
    - 1996 Rice vs. Kansas St. QB Club, 200231
    - 9.6.97 Rice vs. Air Force #2, 200230
    - 9.6.97 Rice vs. Air Force #3, 200229
    - 9.6.97 Rice vs. Air Force #4, 200228
    - 1997 Rice vs. Northwestern TV Copy, 200227
    - 1997 Rice football vs. BYU Coaches Show, 200226
    - 10.4.97 Rice vs. Tulsa Highlights #1, 200225
    - 10.4.97 Rice vs. Tulsa Highlights #2, 200224
    - 10.4.97 Rice vs. Tulsa Highlights #3, 200223
    - 1997 Rice FB/CS Utah, 200222
    - 1997 Rice (Hatfield) Northwestern, 200221
    - 1997-1998 Rice Football Season Home Opener, 200220
    - 10.1.97 Rice 27 | BYU 14, 200219
    - 1997 Rice vs. BYU TV Copy, 200218
    - 1997 Rice University vs. Northwestern TV Copy, 200217
    - 1997 Rice University vs. Northwestern TV Copy, 200216
    - 1997 Rice vs. Northwestern Tape 3, 200215
    - 1997 Rice vs. Tulane TV Copy, 200214
    - 1998 Rice vs. SMU TV Copy, 200213
    - 1998 Rice vs. Tulsa Football Sideline #1, 200212
    - 1998 Rice Football vs. Northwestern Highlights Tape #1, 200211
    - 1998 Rice Football vs. Northwestern Highlights Sideline #3, 200210
    - 1998 Rice vs. Purdue Endzone Tape 2, 200209
    - 1998 Rice vs. Purdue Endzone Tape 1, 200208
    - 1998 Rice vs. San Jose St. Endzone Tape #2, 200207
    - 1998 Rice vs. San Jose St. Endzone Tape #1, 200206
    - 1998 Rice vs. Tulsa Football Sideline #2, 200205
    - 1998 Rice Football vs. Purdue Highlights Tape #1, 200204
  - Football 1998-2000, 200159 (Box 115)
    - 1998 August NCAA College Football Sportsmanship Video, 200202
    - 10.10.98 Rice Special Teams vs. San Jose State Copy 3, 200201
    - 10.10.98 Rice Offense vs. San Jose State Exch 1, 200200
    - 1998 Rice vs. Northwestern Endzone Tape 1, 200199
    - 1998 Rice vs. Tulsa FB Endzone #1, 200198
    - 1998 Rice vs. Tulsa FB Sideline #4, 200197
    - 1998 Rice football vs. Purdue Highlights Tape #3, 200196
    - 1998 Rice vs. Northwestern Endzone Tape 2, 200195
    - 1998 Rice vs. Northwestern Highlight Tape 3, 200194
    - 1999 FB Head Shots Raw, 200193
    - 1999 Rice vs. SJS Football Highlights #1, 200192
    - 10.9.99 Rice vs. Hawai'i Continuous Endzone, 200191
    - 10.9.99 Rice vs. Hawai'i Continuous Sideline, 200190
    - 9.25.99 Rice vs. Navy Continuous Endzone, 200189
    - 9.25.99 Rice vs. Navy Continuous Sideline, 200188
    - 10.30.99 Rice vs. SMU Continuous Sideline, 200187
    - 10.23.99 Rice vs. TCU Continuous Sideline, 200186
    - 10.23.99 Rice vs. TCU Continuous Endzone, 200185
    - 10.2.99 Rice vs. Tulsa Continuous Sideline, 200184
    - 10.16.99 Rice vs. San Jose State Sideline, 200183
    - 10.23.99 Rice vs. San Jose State Endzone, 200182
    - 1999 Rice vs. Hawaii TV Copy, 200181
    - 11.6.99 Rice vs. Fresno State Continuous Sideline, 200180
    - 2.4.99 The Coach, 200179
    - 9.16.99 Rice Football Jingle Bells 11 News KHOU Houston, 200178
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Original Sideline Tape 3, 200177
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Original Highlight Tape 3, 200176
    - 9.23.00 Rice Offense vs. Oklahoma Sideline Tape 1, 200175
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Sideline Tape 4, 200174
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Highlight Tape 3, 200173
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Nevada Endzone Tape 1, 200172
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 1, 200171
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Highlight Tape 1, 200170
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Sideline Tape 1, 200169
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 4, 200168
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Sideline Tape 2, 200167
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 2, 200166
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Highlight Tape 2, 200165
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Highlight Tape 1, 200164
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Original Sideline Tape 4, 200163
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Original Endzone Tape 1, 200162
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Original Highlight Tape 3, 200161
    - 0.30.00 Rice vs. San Jose State Highlight Tape 2, 200160
  - Football 2000-2001, 200129 (Box 116)
    - 11.03.01 Rice Football vs. Fresno State Sideline Tape 3, 200158
    - 11.03.01 Rice Football vs. Fresno State Sideline Tape 1, 200157
    - 11.10.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Endzone Tape 1, 200156
    - 09.01.01 Rice vs. Houston Original Highlight Tape 3, 200155
    - 11.24.01 Rice vs. SMU Highlight Tape 2, 200154
    - 09.20.01 ESPN College Game Day – Rice Football, 200153
    - 11.17.01 Rice vs. UTEP Endzone Tape 1, 200152
    - 11.10.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Sideline Tape 4, 200151
    - 11.17.01 Rice vs. UTEP Sideline Tape 4, 200150
    - 09.16.00 Rice Offense vs. Tulsa Original Highlight Tape 1, 200149
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Original Highlight Tape 2, 200148
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Original Sideline Tape 2, 200147
    - 11.17.01 Rice football vs. UTEP Sideline Tape 1, 200146
    - 11.17.01 Rice football vs. UTEP Highlight Tape 3, 200145
    - 11.10.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Highlight Tape 1, 200144
    - 10.27.01 Rice vs. Louisiana Tech Highlight Tape 2, 200143
    - 11.03.01 Rice vs. Fresno State Endzone Tape 1, 200142
    - 11.24.01 Rice vs. SMU Highlight Tape 1, 200141
    - 10.13.01 Rice vs. Navy Original Highlight Tape 3, 200140
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Original Endzone Tape 1, 200139
    - 10.28.00 Rice vs. TCU Original sideline Tape 4, 200138
    - 09.23.00 Rice offense vs. Oklahoma Original Endzone Tape 2, 200137
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Original Sideline Tape 1, 200136
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Original sideline Tape 3, 200135
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Original sideline Tape 3, 200134
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Original Endzone Tape 1, 200133
    - 10.21.00 Rice Offense vs. Hawaii Original Sideline Tape 2, 200132
    - 11.11.00 Rice vs. UTEP Original Sideline Tape 3, 200131
    - 11.04.00 Rice vs. SMU Original Endzone Tape 2, 200130
  - Football 2001, 200087 (Box 117)
    - 9.13.01 QB Club – Duke, Houston, 200128
    - 09.08.01 Rice vs. Duke Original Endzone Tape 2, 200127
    - 10.06.01 Rice vs. Boise State Original Sideline Tape 1, 200126
    - 10.06.01 Rice vs. Boise State Original Sideline Tape 2, 200125
    - 10.06.01 Rice vs. Boise State Original Sideline Tape 3, 200124
    - 10.06.01 Rice vs. Boise State Original Endzone Tape 1, 200123
    - 10.06.01 Rice vs. Boise State Original Endzone Tape 2, 200122
    - 10.27.01 Rice Football vs. Louisiana Tech Highlight Tape 1, 200121
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Sideline Tape 1, 200120
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Sideline Tape 2, 200119
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Sideline Tape 4, 200118
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Endzone Tape 1, 200117
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Endzone Tape 2, 200116
    - 9.29.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Sideline Tape 1, 200115
    - 11.24.01 Rice Football vs. SMU Sideline Tape 1, 200114
    - 11.24.01 Rice Football vs. SMU Sideline Tape 2, 200113
    - 11.24.01 Rice Football vs. SMU Sideline Tape 3, 200112
    - 11.24.01 Rice Football vs. SMU Sideline Tape 4, 200111
    - 11.24.01 Rice Football vs. SMU Endzone Tape 2, 200110
    - 10.20.01 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 1, 200109
    - 10.20.01 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 2, 200108
    - 10.20.01 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 3, 200107
    - 10.20.01 Rice vs. Nevada Sideline Tape 4, 200106